Bruno Zurita

520-591-0163 | zuritdaruno2896@gmail.com

Summary

A successful self-criven individud looking for advancement within Information Technology. Experienced System Administrator with three year background in Information Technology. Expert in austomer service and security systems. Known for best-in-dass hardware and software knowledge and detail-oriented project rall outs. Extensive experience in networking property systems, leadership, and systems security dong with an experness to learn newer technology. A fast learner that can adapt to any environment.

Skills

- Team management
- Offiæ365
- Hardware expertise
- Microsoft & Windows Servers
- TCP/IP & DNS/DHCP
- LAN/WAN

- Saripting
- Diagnosingissues
- VMWare
- Back Up & Storage
- Fluent in English & Spanish

Experience

SERVER ADMINISTRATOR | 08/2020 to Current Child Parent Centers Inc. - Tucson, AZ

Andyzedintricate server issues and supported large enterprise and business-aritical applications. Provided effective resolutions to issues and escalated problems with knowledgeable support and quality service. Provided austomer support such as troubleshooting computers, printers, scanners, and phones to users working remotely and on site. Deployed Print Server within the Organization to minimize deployment time for computers. Reconfigured the Deployment Server (Ghost) to be able to reimage computers at a faster pace and assist in accomplishing the team's deadlines for deployments. Of eated script to automate procedures for easier and faster computer set up, like installing agents in the background without any user internation. Assisting with removing retired devices from Active Directory; general Exchange mailbox issues; Zoom platform assistance. Upgraded Servers from 2012R2 to 2019. Utilize Kace Quest for ticket solutions. Repaired the Apple Server to be able to configure and deploy i Pacts to multiple centers. Change desk phone names, voicemail pins and rerouting desktop all to all phones. Troubleshooting VMware with command lines to resolve minor issues with virtual machines. Of eating new Virtual Machines as new servers. Upgrade Vænter and VSphere from 6.0 to 7.0. Conducted maintenance on ESXI hosts and dusters.

PROPERTY SYSTEMS LEAD (SENIOR TECHNICIAN) | 06/2018 to 07/2020 Gaylord Opryland Resort - Nashville, TN

Fostered and maintained collaborative professiond working relationship with project leadership team and dient. Provide level 2 support for Network and Desktop support remotely and on site for 1,000+ users. Utilized VMware environment to diagnose, monitor and resolve servers to ensure daily tasks were not interrupted by a failing server. Utilized and integrated CommVault software for emergency databack up. Imaged Win 7 and Win 10 computers while following Marriott policies to meet standards. Configured VLANs and ports throughout the network. Assisted Server Administrator by updating patches on the Images server to ensure Images were up to date. In charge of reprogramming Point of Sale (POS) when applicable, employ full set ups for program deployment, and maintain accurate inventory. Utilized MAARK 1.2 to remediate devices that were not meeting policy standard. Given the managerid title for emergency calls such as network outage, certain software application not working due to server failure. Configured active directory users, print server; added, removed and modified printers; and added permissions for users and computers through active directory.

COMMUNICATIONS SUPERVISOR | 07/2014 to 04/2018 U.S Army

Diagnose, troubleshoot software, and other system issues. Monitored equipment and notified proper personnel to correct problems. Provided training to personnel on proper procedures and protocols to meet the standard for system security induding phishing trajan virus, and basic equipment standards. Maintained workplace safety by involving employees in order to maximize engagement and team marde. Worked dosely with Battalian S-6 to provide established Secure and Unsecured networks for missions, which induded VoIP via Safellite. Monitored daily operations and performed safety audits to check that staff followed administrative policies and regulations.

Education and Training

 $\label{lem:myComputerCareer -- Raleigh, NC | Information Technology of Systems Administration \\ \textit{Certification: MTASecurity, CompTIAA+, 2018}$